A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, National Affairs, Resources and the Environment, Office Files of William C. Pendleton FA658
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation records, National Affairs, Resources and the Environment, Office Files of William C. Pendleton
1965-1967
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation
FA658
0.44 Cubic Feet
Conditions Governing Access note
Material is open for scholarly research, with prior archival review.
Material more than ten years old is open for scholarly research.
Select individual files are restricted, as noted. Permission to access these files must be obtained from the Ford Foundation before scholarly access is permitted.
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
Ford Foundation archive was deposited at RAC in 2011. Ford Foundation records, correspondence, reports, program files and officers papers were transferred to, and accessioned by, RAC beginning in 2011. Accessions continue as necessary.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
Materials requiring specialized equipment for access (film, audio, video, slides) may be restricted from scholarly research dependent on availability of the applicable equipment. Brittle or damaged items, or materials otherwise in need of preservation care, may be restricted from scholarly research at the discretion of the RAC Head of Archival Services/RAC Head of Reference.
Ford Foundation
- Subject Files, I
  - Economic Development Administration (EDA) Program Memoranda, 1965-1967 (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 1)
  - Other Program Memoranda, 1965-1967 (Box 1)
- Meetings and Trips, II
  - Meetings and Trips (Box 1)
  - South Bend Quota Conference, Jun 24-25, 1965 (Box 1)
  - International Economic Association -- Rome, Italy, Sep 1-8, 1965 (Box 1)
  - IEA East-West Meeting, Bellagio, Italy [PHOTOS], Sep 5-11, 1965 (Box 1)
  - Trip -- California, Oct 3-8, 1965 (Box 1)
  - New York City Transit Strike, Feb 24, 1966 (Box 1)
  - Sacramento -- Charles Hitch, May 24, 1966 (Box 1)
  - EDA Summer Institute -- Williams College, MA, Jun-Jul 1966 (Box 1)
  - Trip -- Alaska, Jul 1966 (Box 1)
  - Conference on Government Expenditures, Brookings Institute, Washington DC, Aug 14-16, 1966 (Box 1)
  - Trip -- Europe (IEA-CNRS, Regional Science Association), Aug 21-Sep 11, 1966 (Box 1)
  - Residential Needs in Highway Transportation -- Saratoga Springs, NY, Oct 25-26, 1966 (Box 1)
  - Southern Economic Association, Atlanta GA, Nov 11, 1966 (Box 1)
  - NASBO, Nov 19, 1966 (Box 1)